Applause for that channel.
We have a guest here today who is a perfect fit for the first installment of the resurrection of the "The Root of All Evil," so let's give him a call.
Today's guest is this gentleman.
Hello.
I'm Takagishi from Gibondi.
It's been a while.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mr. Takagishi.
Takagishi.
I'm Takagishi.
Yes?
How have you been?
Yes, I am.
I'm glad.
Bri... right, once on the terrestrial channel.
The first guest. Yes, it was the first time.
Yes, it was a great misfortune.
It was a day of great anxiety.
It was a treasure day for me. Thanks to your power.
Let's do the baseball team's vocalization.
Let's do the baseball team's "ish, ish, ish" from the gut.
All right, whatever you think is best.
A mouse is fine. A mouse is fine.
Or a kiss? A kiss?
Nice ball! Great ball!
Right in the center!
It's been two and a half years since you were our first guest.
It's been two and a half years since then.
No, we don't.
That's right.
Not since then.
No, we haven't worked together, but I've been watching how you've been doing.
The Face Shuttle.
You've been going through the gymnastics world with great speed, haven't you?
I've been watching you with great interest.
But, Mr. Takagi, Tiger Drum...
Thank you very much.
He's doing great in high school too.
No, no, no. He's nothing compared to Hashimoto.
You're married too? That's right.
I did. That's great.
We put our heart rings on each other.
Fitting? Fitted.
We're hooked. Thank you.
Congratulations. What do you want to do today?
Today I'm going to check to see how much he's improved at baseball since we last saw him.
I thought I'd check to see if he's gotten any better at baseball since then.
He hasn't played baseball. He's neither good nor bad at it.
I was astonished by his talent.
Once it's matured, it should be a shiny diamond.
Even me? That's because you're him.
With his talent and passion, I'm sure he'll become a great player.
I've been looking forward to today. I'm glad.
Let's play baseball!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! On the beast's card!
Nonononononononononononononononononononononononononononononononon?
I can't believe I'm still saying that.
And I can't erase it!
Come on, let's go find out!
Non-non!
Do you want me to upload it?
Yes, of course.
Okay, let's go around on the side.
Then follow me.
What, what, what?
Bye-bye.
Big turn!
What? What did you do?
Big! Big! Big!
What's going on?
Why aren't you following me?
What's wrong?
You're gonna get hurt if you don't get up there.
What are you doing?
It's okay if I follow you.
You want me to copy you?
Yes, you can follow me.
Yes, and make it big.
I have a stomach ache.
I'll imitate you.
Let's go home.
Yes, yes, big.
That's it.
Next.
Lift your feet up like this.
Touch your toes like this.
Like this. Big, yeah, big.
Why aren't you following me?
What, you can't?
From the beginning?
Go learn it here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay?
Here we go. Here we go.
That's it.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's good.
Okay, now, a little step.
Forward and backward, forward and backward, forward and backward, yes, yes!Front to back, back to front, front to back, back to front, yes, yes!
That's good. I knew you also dance, so you have a great sense of rhythm.
I'm doing it.
Are you doing it?
Yes, I'm doing it.
Don't worry, I believe in you too. You're doing it.
Yay.
All right, that's great.
Now that we've finished forming up, let's work on bodybuilding.
Isn't that all?
That was just for cardiopulmonary functions and to loosen up the body, wasn't it?
Yes, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
Then, let's do the jumps for explosiveness that we did last time.
Let's do it.
Take a big one, feeling the lychee firmly.
Boom!
Okay, I'll start with shout 1.
When I say one, one.
Then two.
Five times, and when I say stop, okay.
Okay.
If I say stop, good.
Here we go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
All right.
Is it done?
Yes, I got it. But you should be able to speak from the bottom of your stomach.
Yes.
To speak out, you have to use your core, don't you? These abdominal muscles, the tandens.
In baseball, everything starts from this tanden.
Everything starts from the tanden.
Tanden.
Yes. So put your strength into your tandens, Ausch!
Auch.
Go ahead.
Ausch!
Aush!
If it's 1, AUSH!
Ausch!
On two, Aosh!
What?
Aosh!
Two. AUGH!
Three. AUGH!
Four... augh!
Okay! Let's do it again!
Five!
Six oh!
7 ow!
Eight!
9 ow!
All right! That's great!
What do you think?
It's like you're waking up, isn't it?
The feeling of power being released from your true body.
That's what you need to feel when you're batting or pitching.
Voice?
Yes, voice is the key to everything.
Yes, sir.
Excellent.
Let's play catch.
Yeah!
Yes, please.
Ano Channel
Oh! Strong shoulders!
I'm going for it!
That one! Oh! That's good!
That's great!
You're a master! Hobby craftsman!
How do you do it? How do you hold the ball?
The ball. Hold it.
Oh, that's a change-up.
The ball is held against this seam with the index and middle fingers
You hold it with your index and middle fingers
Align your index and middle fingers with this line.
Is that right?
That's right.
Compare the throws to see how different they are.
Let me see.
Like this?
Yes! That's great!
Now let's throw one.
Don't use the other fingers.
Don't use any other fingers.
That's a great question! That's right.
You only need to focus on these two fingers.
You don't have to be conscious of them.
The others come in naturally.
That's right.
So much so that if you hit your hand, the ball will fall off.
That's how much force you need to put in.I'll put it in with that amount of force.
Yes, sir.
Yes, come on!
What should I do with my body?
Well, there's nothing to fix.
Let's just do the grips one at a time.
For humans, yes.
Nice poke!
That was a good turn!
That was a great turn!
Yay!
One at a time, one at a time.
Let's grab the one you just grabbed and throw it once.
Let's see which one's easier to throw.
Good ball! It's still great.
Next, two balls.
Two.
There you go!
Hey!
What do you think? It feels right.
I don't know, two of them are straight.
It's bigger.
That's what it feels like.
It's for pitchers.
Yay!
It's all spinning at once.
Now let's increase the distance.
Here we go.
Oh-ho-ho!
That's great.
That's a lot of flying.
No way.
I can make it longer. I can make it longer.
That's good.
Let's make it longer.
There you go.
Come on, come on.
Oh-ho-ho ho-ho ho-ho
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
You did it, didn't you?
I didn't do the boy bake.
He's so physically strong.
Yo!
You're really athletic, aren't you?
That's pretty impressive.
Even this is farther than the distance of a pitcher.
Heh.
So I can reach the first pitch and stuff.
That's a relief.
Wow, takiej!
You got it!
I'll try it again... for the first time in two years.
It was the first time at that time!
That's him!
This end is...
Well, if you're a beginner, you can't reach it.
It's pretty amazing at this point.
Here we go.
I'm getting it.
That's it.
Do you see how your body's off-center?
That's because you don't know where you're going.
He's trying to throw it my way.
Why can't I just throw it to you?
It's important to have the desire to throw.
I see.
To throw far, the faster the ball is, the farther it goes.
It's all about the image. What's the fastest thing you have in your mind, Ano?
A rat!
Just throw a rat.
Throw a mouse at me.
The image of throwing something fast
Imagine you're throwing a fast mouse to me.
You can imitate a mouse's squeak
Chew.
Come on.
Nine!
Quick! Mr. Camera!
Nice work, Mr. Camera!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You were going fast just now.
You were going fast.
That's great.
It didn't go up at all.
It's not going up. Oh, go farther.
There's a net here.
I think that means you're subconsciously
I think you put a limit on yourself unconsciously.
So it's important to imagine that you're trying to throw it farther away.
Do you have a distant place in mind, Ano?
A far away place?
Image
The human mind.
The human heart?
My heart is very close to you.
Really?Really?
It feels far away.
It feels far away?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Far away.
Is there anything else? Far away.
A place?
Yeah, anywhere.
Anywhere...
Anywhere.
Hokkaido?
Hokkaido's great! Throw it to Hokkaido, then.
Send the rats to Hokkaido!
What do you mean?
Come on! Here, Hokkaido!
Ten!
Oh! Nice ball!
Nettall!
That's great! Yes!
You're so talented! You did it!
I can swallow it in a second. I have the honesty to make it my own.
Yay! That's sweet. He's a sweetheart.
You did it! What do you think? What do you think? Throw it.
I don't know. I'm just throwing it out there.
It's fun to be able to throw that thing without even knowing it.
That's fun.
You're a real genius.
I don't have an image.
I'll remember this.
Yes, sir.